MATEUSZ KRÓLIKOWSKI

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

After many journeys and variety of professions tried. I have decide to settle down a bit and discovered a passion for coding. That's why I have joined infoShare Academy - to further develop my skills and eventually find my first job as a Junior Developer.

CONTACT

+48 884 854 347

✓ krolikmat@gmail.com

Gdańsk

https://github.com/krolik2

www.linkedin.com/in/mateusz-krolikowski

EXPERIENCE

STAPLES - Data Management Specialist JUN 2017 - APR 2019

Responsible for article creation and maintenance. Testing and Quality Assurance of business application Participating in Scrum Framework

Dillan Grill /Germany/ - Courier
APR 2016 - APR 2017

Food delivery, restaurant maintenance

INPOST S.A. - Courier OCT 2015 - APR 2016

Transporting courthouse documents, delivering packages

 ODIN PARTNER RADØY AS/ Northern Ireland/ -Fireguard APR 2014 - JUL 2014

Fires safety inspections, organizing safe working environment in drilling platform tanks.

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Redux

React

Git

Scrum

EDUCATION

infoShare Academy
OCT 2018 - MAY 2019

OCT 2018 - MAY 2019

Junior Front-end Developer - 240h bootcamp

During the course, we have created a cat related website and a KittyCatch game in JavaScript, plus an React app which allow user to find a cat breed, which match perfectly his preferences.

WSB University in Gdańsk

OCT 2010 - OCT 2015

Bachelor's degree in Business Management

LANGUAGES

HOBBIES

Cats | Gaming | Cooking | Football

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).